Hello!
Today we're going to be talking about stamp assembly.
There's 3 types of stamps.
There's clear acrylic stamps, there's foam stamps, and there's wood block rubber stamps.
The one I'm going to demonstrate for you today is the wooden block rubber stamps.
When you first get your stamps, what you want to do is go ahead and pull out all your blocks and your stamps.
Sometimes they'll come with a label, so go ahead and pull those out.
I like to set my blocks out by size.
That way I know how I'm going to match them up with my stamps.
The next thing you're going to do is just take apart the stamps if they come already cut this far.
I like to again, match them with the block that it's going to go with.
That way you have an idea of where you're going to go with each stamp.
The thing you want to remember when you're trimming your stamps is on small stamps you don't want trim more of a 1/4 inch to 1/2 inch or your stamp will kind of lose its integrity.
It won't be able to balance good on the wood block.
The first thing you'll need is a good pair of rubber and craft scissors.
What you'll do is you'll choose the stamp that you want to start with.
I'm going to start with this big one here, and you'll get ready to cut.